A Guide to the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Administration, Records, 1997-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
Library of Virginia
- Series XVI. Veterans' Affairs Records, 2002-2005., Extent: 71 folders. (Box 71-79)
  - Cemetery--Amelia 2002-2004 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Cemetery--Suffolk 2002-2004 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Cemetery--Suffolk 2002-2004 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Briefing Book, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Correspondence and Electronic Mail, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Correspondence and Electronic Mail, 2002-2003 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Follow-up, 2002 July 31 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Leadership Advisory Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Legislation, 2002-2003 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Meeting, 2002 July 31 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Meeting, 2002 September 12 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Meeting, 2002 October 15 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Meeting, 2002 October 30 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Meeting, 2002 November 16 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Meeting, 2002 November 19 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Meeting, 2002 December 16 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Membership, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Presentation, 2002 July 31 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Publicity and General Information, 2002-2003 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Report to Governor, 2002 December (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Report to Governor, 2002 December (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Structures and Strategies Committee, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission for Veterans' Affairs--Veterans' Preference in Employment, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Inquiries Concerning Veterans' Services, 2002-2004 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Joint Leadership Council of Veterans' Service Organizations, 2003-2005 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Veterans' Affairs, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Veterans' Issues, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Veterans' Issues--Ulus Battle, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Veterans' Services, Board of, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Veterans' Services, Board of, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Veterans' Services, Board of, 2003-2005 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Veterans' Services, Board of--Meeting #1, 2003 September 16 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Veterans' Services, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Veterans' Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Veterans' Services, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Veterans' Services Foundation, 2003-2005 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit: Auditor of Public Accounts, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit: Division of State Internal Audit, 2002-2003 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit and Conversion: Diversified Health Systems, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit and Conversion: Diversified Health Systems, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit and Conversion: Diversified Health Systems, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit and Conversion: Diversified Health Systems, Bankruptcy, 2002-2003 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit and Conversion: Diversified Health Systems, Correspondence, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit and Conversion: Diversified Health Systems, Correspondence, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit and Conversion: Diversified Health Systems, Payment History, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Audit and Conversion: General Information, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Financial Statements, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission Study, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Manual: Volume One, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Manual: Volume One, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Manual: Volume One, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Manual: Volume One, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Manual: Volume Two, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Manual: Volume Two, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Proposals, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Proposals, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Proposals, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Proposals, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Proposals, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Richmond, 2002-2005 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Roanoke, 2003-2005 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Roanoke: Board of Trustees, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Roanoke: Board of Trustees, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Roanoke: Board of Trustees, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Veterans Care Center--Roanoke: Board of Trustees, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Series XVII. Weekly Reports Files, 2002-2005., Extent: 73 folders. (Box 79-86)
  Consists of weekly reports submitted to the Secretary of Administration by the agencies and boards that operated under its heading, including the Charitable Gaming Commission, the Commonwealth Competition Council, the Compensation Board, the State Board of Elections, the Department of Employment Dispute Resolution, the Department of General Services, the Department of Human Resource Management, the Council on Human Rights, the Local Government Commission, the Department of Veterans Services, and the Virginia War Memorial Foundation. Each agency head was required to submit a report on a weekly basis so that the Secretary was up-to-date on the progress of projects and informed of any other issues or problems the agency had encountered. The reports contain information on legislation affecting the agency, matters of operation such as staffing and procurement, notice of special events, training, and stakeholder issues. The level of detail varies by agency. Some agencies and boards produced one or two page reports. Others, such as the Department of General Services and the Department of Human Resource Management, submitted highly detailed reports containing five or more pages. Notable reports include those created by the State Board of Elections, which document in detail issues the Board encountered during state and national elections, as well as the switch to a new voting registration system. Additionally, the Department of General Services reports contain notes on fleet management, Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act (PPEA) projects, the Capitol Square renovations, and other real property related information. The Department of Human Resource Management files contain documentation of the state's budget crisis and subsequent lay-offs in 2002, as well as a compensation reform survey summary and a report on state health benefits, from March and October 2004, respectively. The reports are filed alphabetically by the name of the agency or board, and are arranged chronologically within each year.
  - Charitable Gaming Commission, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Charitable Gaming Commission, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Charitable Gaming, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Charitable Gaming, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Charitable Gaming, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Charitable Gaming, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth Competition Council, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Commonwealth Competition Council, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Commonwealth Competition Council, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Compensation Board, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Compensation Board, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Compensation Board, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Compensation Board, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights, Council on, 2002 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Human Rights, Council on, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Human Rights, Council on, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Human Rights, Council on, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Local Government, Commission on, 2002 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Local Government, Commission on, 2002 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Local Government, Commission on, 2002 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Local Government, Commission on, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Local Government, Commission on, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Veterans' Affairs, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Veterans' Affairs, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Veterans' Services, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Veterans' Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Veterans' Services, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Veterans' Services, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Virginia War Memorial Foundation, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Virginia War Memorial Foundation, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Virginia War Memorial Foundation, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Virginia War Memorial Foundation, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 12)